http://www.webster.edu/_resources/web-privacy-policy.html

COVID-19 Information:
For the latest about coronavirus case counts at Webster University, statements from
the University about the pandemic, and links to advice from the Centers for Disease
Control (CDC), please follow this link to the University’s COVID-19 Resource Pages.
Website Privacy Statement
In addition to the statement below, Webster University strictly adheres to the United States Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 (FERPA).
Webster University takes seriously the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
that will affect our students and employees who are EU residents and/or citizens.
It is our goal to be sensitive and respectful of your personal information and to
adhere to all facets of the GDPR regulation. Please be aware that all personal data
you provide are subject to our privacy policy which can be found at webster.edu/gdpr.
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with
how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as
used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on
its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person,
or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully
to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your
Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website
or app?
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter
your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you
with your experience.
When do we collect information?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter,
respond to a survey, fill out a form, Use Live Chat or enter information on our site. Provide
us with feedback on our products or services
How do we use your information?
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase,
sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the
website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
How do we protect visitor information?
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers at
webster.edu however, we do use third party transaction processing providers that deploy
their own security and privacy policies.We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible
by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and
are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit
information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain
the safety of your personal information.
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed
on our servers.
Do we use 'cookies'?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your
computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's
or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain
information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items
in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based
on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved
services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic
and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the
future.
We use cookies to:• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.• Keep track of advertisements.• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer
better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party
services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or
you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet
Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's
Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the user's
experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services
will not function properly.
However, you can still place orders .
Third-party disclosure
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable
information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website
hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting
our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information
confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to
comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights,
property or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other
parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third-party links
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles.
They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use
of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to
our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART
cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.
We have implemented the following:• Remarketing with Google AdSense• Google Display Network Impression Reporting• Demographics and Interests Reporting• DoubleClick Platform Integration
We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as
the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie)
or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions
with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings
page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative
opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
California Online Privacy Protection Act
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online
services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California
to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that
operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers
to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information
being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply
with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:Users can visit our site anonymously.Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or
as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on
the page specified above.
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:• On our Privacy Policy PageUsers are able to change their personal information:• By calling us
How does our site handle do not track signals?We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising
when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal
Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule,
which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect
children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under 13.
Fair Information Practices
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the
United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the
development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information
Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with
the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following
responsive action, should a data breach occur:We will notify the users via in-site notification• Within 7 business days
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals
have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors
who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have
enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to
courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data
processors.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements
for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being
sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.• We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original
transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:• NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can
email us at• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using
the information below.
webster.edu470 E. Lockwood Ave.Webster Groves, Missouri 63119USAdigital@webster.edu
©
